[{"answer": " Hi, Amelie.  How are you", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Im good.  How are you", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hi, Amelie.  How are you", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Im doing fine, thank you.  Did you have a nice weekend", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Im good.  How are you", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Yes, it was very fun.  My cousin took me to see the zoo downtown", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Im doing fine, thank you.  Did you have a nice weekend", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Great!  That sounds like fun", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Yes, it was very fun.  My cousin took me to see the zoo downtown", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Yes, it was a very interesting place", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Great!  That sounds like fun", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Well, today I thought we would do a little dictation to practice our listenin", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Yes, it was a very interesting place", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " OK, sounds good", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Well, today I thought we would do a little dictation to practice our listenin", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Why dont you take out a piece of paper and write your name and todays dat", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 23, "question": " OK, sounds good", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Why dont you take out a piece of paper and write your name and todays dat", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Amelie, today is June 9th.  Why did you write September 6th", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " I didnt.  I wrote 9/6, June 9th", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Amelie, today is June 9th.  Why did you write September 6th", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Oh, here in the U.S. we write the month first, then the day.  So it should be 6/9", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 33, "question": " I didnt.  I wrote 9/6, June 9th", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Oh, sorry!  In France we write the day, then the month", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Oh, here in the U.S. we write the month first, then the day.  So it should be 6/9", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Thats OK.  Maybe we should take this opportunity to talk about number", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Oh, sorry!  In France we write the day, then the month", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " That will be good.  They are difficult for me in English", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Thats OK.  Maybe we should take this opportunity to talk about number", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK, lets review the numbers 1-10 first.  Lets say them together", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 43, "question": " That will be good.  They are difficult for me in English", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " One, Two, Three, Four, Five, Six, Seven, Eight, Nine, Ten", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 44, "question": " OK, lets review the numbers 1-10 first.  Lets say them together", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Good!  Now lets count in tens to 100", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 45, "question": " One, Two, Three, Four, Five, Six, Seven, Eight, Nine, Ten", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": "Ten, Twenty, Thirty, Forty, Fifty, Sixty, Seventy, Eighty, Ninety, One Hundred", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Good!  Now lets count in tens to 100", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Very good!  I think you know your numbers in English.  But lets talk about som", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Ten, Twenty, Thirty, Forty, Fifty, Sixty, Seventy, Eighty, Ninety, One Hundred", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Zip code?  No, I dont know", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Very good!  I think you know your numbers in English.  But lets talk about som", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Thats a 5-digit number that tells where in the US you live.  You write it wit", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Zip code?  No, I dont know", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Ah, yes.  I remember", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Thats a 5-digit number that tells where in the US you live.  You write it wit", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Good.  How about area code?  Do you know what that number is", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Ah, yes.  I remember", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Yes, I know this one.  I have to use it for calling my cousin from France", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Good.  How about area code?  Do you know what that number is", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Right!  The area code is a three-digit number that we have to use when callin", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Yes, I know this one.  I have to use it for calling my cousin from France", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Yes, I always had to dial 705 to call my cousin", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Right!  The area code is a three-digit number that we have to use when callin", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " MmmHmm.  Speaking of phone calls, do you know what number to call if yo", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Yes, I always had to dial 705 to call my cousin", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " You know, I dont know.  In France we dial 801", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 71, "question": " MmmHmm.  Speaking of phone calls, do you know what number to call if yo", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Here in the U.S. we have to dial 911 for an emergency", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 72, "question": " You know, I dont know.  In France we dial 801", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " I had better remember that then just in case", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Here in the U.S. we have to dial 911 for an emergency", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Yes, make sure you remember that.  Have you heard of 411", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 74, "question": " I had better remember that then just in case", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " No, never", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Yes, make sure you remember that.  Have you heard of 411", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Thats the number you can dial for information.  Say if you need to fin", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 76, "question": " No, never", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " How useful", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Thats the number you can dial for information.  Say if you need to fin", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Yes.  And this number has become part of American slang too.  Have yo", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 80, "question": " How useful", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " No", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Yes.  And this number has become part of American slang too.  Have yo", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " It means, Whats going on?  or Whats the latest information", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 85, "question": " No", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Oh, thank you!  I love learning American slang.  Its the real language peopl", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 86, "question": " It means, Whats going on?  or Whats the latest information", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " No problem.  Its definitely important to know", "docId": "11-07", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Oh, thank you!  I love learning American slang.  Its the real language peopl", "qSentId": 89}]
